# KIRAN MAHALE

#### DEVOPS ENGINEER



Mumbai, India 💡

careers.kiranmahale@yahoo.in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kiran -mahale-a30115126

+91 9869824766

#### **PROFILE**

Total Experience of 13 years in IT industry.

Experienced DevSecOps Professional with 2 to 3 years specializing in AWS, automation, DevOps tools, and Security tools. Proficient in Linux, git, Github, Gitlab, Azure DevOps, Sonarqube, and scripting languages (Shell, Bash, Powershell, Python).

Experience in .NET with 10 years of experience specializing in MVC, angular, jquery, javascript, Web API, and SQL.

Strong problem-solving skills, commitment to accountability, and good managing skills of a team.

Note: I had 10 years of experience in .NET and then moved to DevSecOps skills.

# LANGUAGES

English native language

German speaking, reading, writing

Chinese speaking, reading,

#### **EDUCATION**

Welingkar Institute of Management Development and Research

2021 - 2023 | PGDM IT Project Management

Usha Mittal Institute Of Technology , SNDT UNIVERSITY

2006 - 2010 | B.TECH Information Technology

Bhavans College, MUMBAI UNIVERSITY

2005 - 2006 | HSC Science

J.B. Khot High School, MUMBAI UNIVERSITY

2003 - 2004 | SSC

# SKILLS

- Azure DevOps
- AWS laaC
- Pvthon
- Powershell
- CI CD Pipeline
- GitHub administration, GHAS
- Gitlab CI CD Pipeline
- Security tools SonarQube, Jfrog Xray
- Terraform
- .NET
- WEB API
- SQL Server
- jQuery, Javascript
- Angular

### **EXPERIENCES**

Sep 2019 - Present Accenture India
Associate Manager

- Responsibilities include direct communication with clients, Leading Team, and development [new requirements and production calls].
- Handling the Ops work like client issues offline or Incidents/SRs within a team with zero SLA breach

Feb 2016 - Sep 2019

Lauren Technologies Pvt. Ltd

Team Leader

 Responsibilities include direct communication with clients, Leading Team, and software development [new requirements and production calls].

Sept 2015 - Jan

CMC

2016

IT Analyst

 Responsibilities include direct communication with clients, Leading Team, and software development [new requirements and production calls].

Mar 2014 - Aug

Financial Technologies India

2015

Ltd.

Software Engineer

 Responsibilities include software development [new requirements and production calls].

Feb 2011 - Mar

Idealake Information

2014

Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Software Developer

 Responsibilities include software development [new requirements and production calls], and handling team.

# CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified DevSecOps Professional
- AWS Developer Associate
- AZ-900

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

• ACE Winner in Accenture

#### INTERESTS

- Playing Carrom
- Internet Surfing
- Listening to Music
- Painting

.